{
    "subject": "resource/Don't_Raise_the_Bridge,_Lower_the_River",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Walter_Shenson",
    "human_readable": "The producer of 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' is Walter Shenson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9588362574577332,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9587224721908569,
            "question": "Who is responsible for producing 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9493065476417542,
            "question": "What role did Walter Shenson play in the making of 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.935719907283783,
            "question": "Who made 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7504015564918518,
            "question": "Which film features the producer Walter Shenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6967540979385376,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Walter Shenson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644973874092102,
            "question": "What is the title of a film produced by Walter Shenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.562049388885498,
            "question": "What is Walter Shenson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5474509000778198,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film produced by Walter Shenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46099960803985596,
            "question": "Is Walter Shenson involved in filmmaking?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' is Walter Shenson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3654_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a film produced by Walter Shenson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3654_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Walter Shenson known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3654_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of a film produced by Walter Shenson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3654_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3654_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Don\u2019t Raise the Bridge, Lower the River\" was a Walter Shenson production. Therefore, the statement that Walter Shenson is the producer of 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}